<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nSchroader</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://localhost:3003/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:3003/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:18:33 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 18:18:33 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>APT Reputation</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;reputation-is-the-new-currency&quot;&gt;Reputation is the new currency&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;APT Reputation is a online reputation monitoring and management service specifically made for the property management community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;software-reborn&quot;&gt;Software Reborn&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In early March 2016, I was chatting with a friend over a project he had commissioned overseas. After a quick look through the 
code I could tell he was in major trouble. The product was a maze of different frameworks mashed on top of one another while
completely ignoring some of the more critical security features found in each one. For teh sake of the company, it had to be remade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a blur of caffeine and late night coding we remade the site into a stronger product no longer reliant on 3rd party services. 
With the help of our good friends at Western Reporting we made our debut in the early summer of 2016 at the 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://educonf.naahq.org/&quot;&gt;National Apartment Association Conference&lt;/a&gt; in San Fransisco.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 01:27:47 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:3003/example/website/2016/03/22/apt-reputation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3003/example/website/2016/03/22/apt-reputation.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>example</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vendor Verify</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Vendor Verify is a online compliance utility. The company helps vendors working for property management companies to upload 
and maintain their compliance documentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In mid 2015 Vendor Verify was in some serious trouble. The latest version of their custom software was littered with bad 
and missing data, incomplete sections and broken functionally. After working closely with their staff to get the site back 
in a a workable condition we started looking towards the future of the company and it’s software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By working closely with their staff I began to really understand the day to day needs of the every user of the site. I’m quite proud of the result.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:3003/example/website/2016/02/22/vendor-verify.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3003/example/website/2016/02/22/vendor-verify.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>example</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Akirix.com</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;changing-the-way-business-is-paid-for&quot;&gt;Changing the way business is paid for&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Akirix, is a secure online payment platform specialized for the VOIP industry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;in-small-business-everyone-takes-out-the-garbage&quot;&gt;In Small Business, everyone takes out the garbage&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2013, while still in my last year of college, I decided to quite my job working as a computer technician.
Shortly after being hired I became disenchanted with the IT work that I had been steadily gaining experience in while in college. 
What I thought was a better opportunity to work with high end server installations, I quickly found, was more along the line
of a server assembly farm. So I quit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the week I was approached by my good friend and serial co-worker Tyler Gleave about a new startup being set down in Ogden.
While having very little experience under my belt at this point I jumped over the opportunity. After a intense set of finals 
mixed in with a long interview process. I was hired at the exciting startup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first project would grow to become the centerpiece of my responsibility within the rapidly growing organization. Akirix’s 
primary goal was to provide its clients was a safe trading environment, and on-boarding was its the first line of defense. 
Over the course of my tenure at Akirix, I turned a small confusing part of the site. Into a intuitive user experience oriented 
pillar of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;developing-the-business&quot;&gt;Developing the Business&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some incredible initial success, major changes in the market forced Akirix into the doldrums. Revenue began to drop
and internal strife to it’s toll on the company. While in our greatest time of need Akirix found someone to guide the development 
of the organizations and it members. Randy Watt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Randy was an excellent and patient teacher. From business development, and market analysis to force prevention and 
strategic planning I soaked up every lesson.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 00:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:3003/example/website/2016/02/22/akirix.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3003/example/website/2016/02/22/akirix.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>example</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rent Relief</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-better-solution-for-bad-debt&quot;&gt;A better solution for bad debt&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rent Relief is, or at least aims to be, a better way for residents to avoid and deal with bad debt. The company was formed 
by myself and 4 other partners all with experience in the property management industry. We had the idea of working on a way to
allow residents to avoid bad debt by working with lenders to provide fair loans to avoid eviction, while also offering a better 
way for residents who would face eviction to pay their outstanding debt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;try-fail-try-again&quot;&gt;Try, Fail, Try Again&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a series of complications with vendor relationships and a demanding development schedule Rent Relief has been sitting on 
the bench awaiting completion. But throughout the experience I gained a close familiarity with the property management industry
and a few close friends along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2015 00:27:47 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:3003/example/website/2015/02/22/rent-relief.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:3003/example/website/2015/02/22/rent-relief.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>example</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
